[Music]
Then Ribbon, today we will give you a quick review of ICICI Lombard
's Health Advantage Health Insurance Plan.
This is a very good
plan, which was the
health insurance plan of the Indian General Insurance Company. You
all know that ICC has taken over the Indian General Insurance
Company. Please share it with ICC.
We will also tell you at the end of the video
that if you are an existing customer of ICICI Lombard, you can
subscribe because this plan has so many
good features that it will attract you a lot. There are
three variants in the subscription.
Talking about festivals, Prime's Lakh-Lakh plan
is available from Rs. 45 to 50 lakhs and the subscription is
available except for the time till the end.
Talking about entries, any
person between Rs. 22650 can take this policy. The patient can
stay in the hospital for up to 25 years.
Talking about hospitalization,
you can stay for 30 minutes. Talking about room, there is
no limit in the subscription and 2% and you
can also select the
hospitalized in the 30-day plan and in
post hospitalization
and
treatments i.e. Ayurveda, Siddha, Unani
In homeopathy, there are
some guidelines in schools where they get
their swing done, either
they need a government hospital, they need a government approved
center, there should be a minimum of 5 students there, there should be a
dedicated Ayush
Therapies center and that chapter
maintains the data of its clients. If we
talk about treatment, then in this plan
you can click for 586 day care,
see there is a treatment in which you need to be
admitted in the hospital for 24 hours,
you can get your treatment done and
go home, which they talk about soon, then you
can subscribe, if we
talk about road ambulance, then you can click on all three variants for one cent of chilli and
maximum up to Rs. 10000.
Animal is a very good feature,
animal vaccination, if a dog
fights you due to which you have to do
something in the hospital, then the company
claims up to Rs. 10000 in the invariant, the
restore benefit, if you take all the
goods, the should be exhausted by adding the no claim bonus.
So the company will give
you the benefit of restore for up to 10 minutes once a year,
which will
also be done on coverage for this and other balances from the same person, which is
guaranteed. Why relative bonus?
In all the three variants of this plan, you
get a no claim bonus of 20 percent of mint. If you do
not cancel the policy, then it will
increase up to 100 percent and once
increased, it will
not even decrease in the situation of taking a claim, that is why
its name is guaranteed bonus.
Talking about health checkup, you can claim
0.5 percent of vitamins and maximum
1000 cups in all the three variants, which
is available every year and the age of the policy holder should be
above 18 years. Whoever
wants to take the benefit of help, talking about ghee treatment,
you can click for 10 minutes in all the three variants, okay, that is,
if you have any problem due to obesity, then you can
fight it when  You can
subscribe up to a maximum of Rs 1000000 in the school. The
subscribe settings are given and the
policy holder should be Home
Plus. If you have an
emergency situation, you will have to search for it.
In this thing, the company pays on claim,
which means that if the policy holder is
admitted in the hospital, then the company pays on a
lump sum amount, which supports the policy holder
in managing other hospital expenses, which is up
to Rs 20000 once in all three events. You can also add possible benefits in this plan.
Maternity benefit is the first option benefit
in which you can subscribe for a maximum of three deliveries,
which is
not available in Prevent. During this, you
can spend a maximum of Rs 1000000 on the plan and the biggest thing is that
for availing this, there is a condition that you will have to pay at least
3 years' premium together. If
you see it, then you can avail the maternity benefit.  If you
click on the subscribe button to avail the benefit, then the
premium will be 3 years irrespective of the new
born baby. You can also add the option which is
again not available in the prime report.
Vaccination for new
born baby. Now if it is not available then you
can click on more. You
can add the beneficiary which is
not available in the prime report. Home point five minutes and
maximum whichever is less. You can appoint a network doctor
consultation network. You can
subscribe up to ₹500 Rs.25000.
For this you will have to pay an
additional premium. You
can select on it that
in case of break up,
you get clearance even in case of temperature disability.
Talking about the payment, there is no co-payment of any kind in this plan
but you can add it as an optional one in
which your premium will be reduced.
You can add co-payment up to 10 to 20 percent. If you have a free existing disease
before taking the policy then there is
waiting period in it.  The term is of 2 years but if you
want to do optional strike period which
is 3 years or 4 years then in this also your
premium will be deducted.
Talking about policy turnover, you can do it for one year,
2 years or 3 years. There is a
discount of 7.5% on 2 years premium and
10% on 3 years premium
at the company. If you book this plan online, you
get an additional discount of 25%. If we
talk about Delhi-NCR and Mumbai-Thane subscribed Indian State Capital,
then you will have to contact your bank but
in Zone-2 you can
get a discount of 12.5% ​​on lower premium. But if
you need treatment from any region in Zone-1,
then you will have to pay 12.5%.
In Zone-3, which includes Rest of India,
you get a discount of up to 15%
on premium. But if you get treatment done in Zone-1,
which is
done at the lower premium, then you will get 15% discount.  You will have to make the
payment and if you get the treatment done in Zone-2 then
you will have to make the payment of 12.50 per cent. In this plan, you
can also add optional cover of domestic air ambulance which can be claimed after up to 10 minutes.
Talking about the waiting period, there is a waiting period of one month for any
kind of freshness. There is a
waiting period of one month for critical illness. There is a waiting period of two years for specific
diseases like cataract, stone, anklet, ear, eyes, eyes, etc.
related areas. You can also make a claim after
2 years in the reduced plan as
we told earlier.
Bariatric surgery is covered after 3 years
and maternity claim can be made
even after the waiting period of diamond. If
you feel that you have not selected the right plan then you
can cancel your plan during the free look period which is 15 days
and get your money refunded. So it is certain
that such people will get information about Badh's Health
Advantage Plan. If you are an
existing policy holder of ICC robbery and  If
you want to convert to this plan,
it is not possible right now because the company is
not offering the benefits of switching to political benefits. There
may be future chances, but you
cannot change your plan right now. Sunidhi, like all the
information about ICC Lombard's Health
Advantage Health Insurance Plan.
If you liked the video,
we keep bringing such useful information, so
please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you for watching.